MUHAMMAD HANNAN BIN AZMI





PROFILE

A software engineer based in Malaysia. Been in the industry for three years focusing in web development. Looking for expanding my expertise in blockchain technology and integrate it in the web. Very passionate to explore and gain expertise in web assembly, blockchain, and Rust programming language.

SKILLS AND ATTRIBUTES

Communication Language

- Malay (Native)
- English (Proficient)

Technicality

- Full Stack Web Development
- Cloud Computing
- Embedded System

Programming Language

- Javascript/Typescript
- Python
- C++
- Bash

Personal Attribute

Enthusiastic, responsive and hardworking team player. Excellent communication and management skills. Outstanding organisational time management, and problem-solving skills.

CERTIFICATIONS

AWS Certified Solutions Architect

Associate

Microsoft Certified Azure

Fundamentals

EDUCATIONS

BCS Software Engineering

Universiti Malaysia Sarawak

September 2017 - August 2021

CGPA 3.39

Foundation in Science Universiti Malaysia Sarawak

September 2016 – September 2017

CGPA 3.00

Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia SMKA Kuala Lumpur 7A's | 3B's | 1C's

December 2015

EXPERIENCES

Full Stack Web Developer

Novosoft Solutions Sdn Bhd

September 2020 - Present

Lead and involve in multiple company's project including:

- · In-house gaming website
- · Event management system for students
- Corporate website
- Host web development course

Some of the highlights of these projects are:

- Built from static to SPA type of website using React
- Built-in CMS support
- · Serve thousands of concurrent user
- · Implement FaaS with AWS Lambda
- Design and plan beginner and intermediate web development course

Lead Frontend Web Developer

IDM Nexus

September 2022 - January 2023

Create an inventory system for nanotechnology products. Government based project and took four months of development. The purpose of the system is to be the source of information for nanotechnology products in Malaysia. The system is served to the public.

- Prototype based development using Figma
- · Create a design system based on TailwindCSS
- SPA using React
- · Administration interface and public interfaces

Embedded Software Engineer

EDAG Holding Sdn Bhd

November 2021 - May 2022

Perform unit test for automotive system for German automotive company.

- Study model in MATLAB and Simulink for test planning
- Design test case using CMocka
- · Automate test using Python script and Microsoft Excel

Software Engineer Intern

ELMLab Sdn Bhd

February 2020 – July 2020

Involve in IoT product that serve as vending machine locker.

- Develop kiosk-mode interface with Kivy
- Django for backend development
- · Work with Raspberry Pi Model B, LDR sensor, bill acceptor, CCTV, external screen
- Integrate hardware and software using REST and gRPC